DIDZIS ZVAIGZNE



Summary

Quitting without results for me is unheard-of. I am passionate about new technology and learning is a non-stop process for me. I do my best to always aim high and my future goal is to become a full stack developer. Although my previous work experience is not related to my current studies, I am a hard worker and I have gained experience in how to work with a team.

Email 🖂

didzis.zvaigzne@gmail.com

Phone 🗐

+358 44 2070 698

Location 🥎

Turku, Finland

Web site **(**https://didzis.net/

Languages

Latvian - Native

English - Fluent Finnish - Fluent

Skills

HTML & CSS

Python

JavaScript

SQL

GitHub

Interests

Programming & Technology

Cars

Reading books

Weightlifting

Board games

Education

Information and Communications Technology

Turku University of Applied Sciences

09/2019 - Present

Turku

High School Graduate

Perniö High School

08/2015 - 05/2018

Perniö

Work experience

Ship Deck Flooring

SPT-Painting Oy

Flooring ship decks for a cruise ship in 2019 summer

05/2019 - 08/2019

Production Work

Forssan LVI-Valmiste Oy

Producing, assembling and preparing items for distribution

05/2019 - 08/2019

Projects

Parkinsonliitto ry 09/2020 - 12/2020

Participated in a project through school to create a new form and automate applicant registration for Parkinsonliitto ry

COVID-19 worldwide tracker 07/2020

Worldwide tracker that displays COVID-19 related information fetched by an API